torrific.com 2011-06-25

# Download torrents from the web. Fast. Easy.

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
November 10th, 2008 

  1. **INTRODUCTION**  
Acceleration Labs, LLC (“us,” “we,” “Company,” or “Acceleration Labs”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of www.torrific.com (“the Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. 

  2. **INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**  
2.1 **TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
(a)  **TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED**. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site.

(b)  **PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED**. In order for you to access certain premium services and to purchase products that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address); and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and income). Acceleration Labs does not collect or store Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number). If you subscribe to premium services, however, we do require you to provide Financial Data to a payment processing company subject to that vendor’s privacy policy. If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

(c) **COPPA**. Acceleration Labs does not knowingly collect or store any Personal Information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. The Company does not allow children under the age of 13 to register for services. If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to use our service or send us any information. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

(d) **THIRD PARTY ADVERTISEMENTS**. Advertisements and other content appearing on our site may be delivered (or "served") directly to you by third parties. These third parties automatically receive your IP address when this happens and may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third parties advertising or providing content to you through our site.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies and Personal Information by us. It does not cover third party use of cookies or other tracking technologies.

2.2. **USES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
(a)  **COMPANY USE OF INFORMATION**. We may use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services. We may use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Site, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.

(b)  **SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**. We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We will not share Contact Data with other companies who may want to send you information about their products or services, unless you have specifically requested that we share Contact Data with such companies. We also share Contact Data and Financial Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. Those business partners have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Company. In addition, we maintain a procedure for you to review and request changes to your Personal Information; this procedure is described in Section 3.1, below.

(c)  **USER CHOICE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**. You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our partners, you may select the appropriate “opt-out” option each time we ask you for Personal Information.

  3. **CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**.  
Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Service. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties.

3.1. **PUBLIC INFORMATION**. The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

3.2. **LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION**. You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly.

  4. **UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**.   
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
